{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Guess the names that complete these movie titles.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Edward",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "______ Scissorhands"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bill",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Kill ____: Vol. 1"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ryan",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Saving Private ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Benjamin",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "The Curious Case of ________ Button"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sally",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "When Harry Met _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lara",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "____ Croft: Tomb Raider"
  }, {
    "answer": "Will",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Good ____ Hunting"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mary",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "There's Something About ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Conan",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "_____ the Barbarian"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lawrence",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "________ of Arabia"
  }, {
    "answer": "Irene",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Me, Myself and _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Donnie",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "______ Darko"
  }, {
    "answer": "Paul",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "____ Blart: Mall Cop"
  }, {
    "answer": "Polly",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Along Came _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hal",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Shallow ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chuck",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Good Luck _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Luke",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "Cool Hand ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Thomas",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "The ______ Crowne Affair"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sam",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "I Am ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Annie",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "_____ Hall"
  }, {
    "answer": "Rosemary",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "________'s Baby"
  }, {
    "answer": "Johnny",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "______ Mnemonic"
  }, {
    "answer": "Joe",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "___ vs. the Volcano"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bob",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "What About ___?"
  }, {
    "answer": "Harold",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "______ and Maude"
  }, {
    "answer": "Michael",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "_______ Clayton"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dan",
    "category": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
    "question": "___ in Real Life"
  }],
  "quizLength": 27,
  "title": "Movies with Names in the Title Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/movies-with-names-quiz.php"
}